<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<peeragogical-action-review title="Anticipation Paper Progress PAR 2020-06-19" xmlns="htx-scheme-id://org.peeragogy.20120221/patterns/peeragogical-action-review.20200511T003600Z" xmlns:html="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
  <intention-review>
    <html:ul>
      <html:li>Need to get our TODOs to structure and divide ourselves into action on the paper</html:li>
      <html:li>clarify what exactly we’re going to do in the paper!</html:li>
    </html:ul>
  </intention-review>
  <what-happened>
    <html:ul>
      <html:li>Joe Corneli: presentation of 25 minutes with people commenting on things that they think of (e.g., we refreshed on DELPHI, Hero’s Journey)</html:li>
    </html:ul>
  </what-happened>
  <what-happened-perspectives>
    <html:ul>
      <html:li>Joe Corneli is tired!</html:li>
      <html:li>Seems to Analua Dutka-Chirichetti that we are being respectful and logical</html:li>
      <html:li>
        People are amused… Got some jokes!… Charlie Danoff is going crazy :) … Vitor Bruno is making not bad jokes =]… We laughed a bit
        <html:ul>
          <html:li>Pier Bach: has the only method to understand chaos … grain of sand never know what’s going to happen, but avalanche is due, this comes up as insights</html:li>
        </html:ul>
      </html:li>
    </html:ul>
  </what-happened-perspectives>
  <learnings-changes>
    <html:ul>
      <html:li>In peeragogy what often happens is we have this chaotic mass of ideas (swirling pot of hot sugar and we’re trying to make sweet candies!)</html:li>
      <html:li>Still not clear what this paper is arguing</html:li>
      <html:li>When Vikings landed in England they flipped their boat upside down… they worked together <html:a href="https://www.deviationobligatoire.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/02/stockholm-city-hall-radssalen-ceiling.png">https://www.deviationobligatoire.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/02/stockholm-city-hall-radssalen-ceiling.png</html:a></html:li>
    </html:ul>
  </learnings-changes>
  <what-else-should-change-going-forward>
    <html:ul>
      <html:li>Ray Puzio: I’d like to continue further with clarifying the point of the paper</html:li>
      <html:li>Hermano Cintra: Get those TODOs, I didn’t do the things. Did read some Gang of Four. Richard Gabriel <html:a href="https://www.dreamsongs.com/Files/WritersWorkshopTypeset.pdf">https://www.dreamsongs.com/Files/WritersWorkshopTypeset.pdf</html:a> as alternative broader focus.</html:li>
      <html:li>Charlie Danoff: will need to follow up and work on the intro before</html:li>
      <html:li>More meetings later today</html:li>
      <html:li>Worry about the deadline, complete paragraphs</html:li>
      <html:li>Maybe someone can own the timetable…</html:li>
      <html:li>Would it be helpful to have a kanban board?</html:li>
    </html:ul>
  </what-else-should-change-going-forward>
</peeragogical-action-review>
