<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<peeragogical-action-review title="Anticipation Paper Progress PAR 2020-06-26" xmlns="htx-scheme-id://org.peeragogy.20120221/patterns/peeragogical-action-review.20200511T003600Z" xmlns:html="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
  <intention-review>
    <html:ul>
      <html:li>Sharing contributed texts from Paola Ricaurte, Charlie Danoff, and Joe Corneli, and revising them</html:li>
    </html:ul>
  </intention-review>
  <what-happened>
    <html:ul>
      <html:li>We redid the introduction</html:li>
      <html:li>We verbally read texts and made edits and rearrangements</html:li>
      <html:li>We now have a main thesis for the paper!</html:li>
      <html:li>Ray Puzio added a bit of text collecting historical background material</html:li>
      <html:li>We revised our outline</html:li>
    </html:ul>
  </what-happened>
  <what-happened-perspectives>
    <html:ul>
      <html:li>Charlie Danoff was sad to show up late, but was very impressed with how much progress had been made during the meeting when he arrived!</html:li>
      <html:li>Joe Corneli appreciated Paola Ricaurte’s and Charlie Danoff’s contributed texts!</html:li>
    </html:ul>
  </what-happened-perspectives>
  <learnings-changes>
    <html:ul>
      <html:li>We learned a little about patterns and health (it looks like this is an under-developed use case for design patterns)</html:li>
      <html:li>We think there are probably lots of under-developed</html:li>
      <html:li>Use the word “mitigate” instead of “ameliorate” because it is less of a weasel-word and more understandable. It’s more active.</html:li>
      <html:li>Connection to the ongoing discussion about platforms in the mailing list</html:li>
      <html:li>Use AOB to think about 5</html:li>
    </html:ul>
  </learnings-changes>
  <what-else-should-change-going-forward>
    <html:ul>
      <html:li>Ray Puzio should revise historical background section, and some info about scenario planning</html:li>
      <html:li>Analua Dutka-Chirichetti and Charlie Danoff should add case studies</html:li>
      <html:li>Everybody should answer: Are there areas crying out for a reference? Try to use APA style (and please make sure the bibliography doc stays up to date, this is in the folder “annotated bibliography” which includes a file with the same title.)</html:li>
      <html:li>Paola Ricaurte should revise the references (APA format) in Peeragogy Patterns (section 3)</html:li>
      <html:li>Joe Corneli should work on Tufts 2.0 proposal… Maybe this can also be a short case study for this paper.</html:li>
      <html:li>Charlotte Pierce needs another time because Friday doesn’t work</html:li>
      <html:li>Charlie Danoff should Meta-Wrap! Wrap the Wrap!</html:li>
    </html:ul>
  </what-else-should-change-going-forward>
</peeragogical-action-review>
